[{"id":0,"random":891319246,"question":"","category":"*","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Male","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Female","pendex":{}}]},{"id":1,"random":823178587,"question":"","category":"Generic","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Yes","pendex":{"Optimistic":1}},{"answer":"No","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":2,"random":448995629,"question":"","category":"Generic","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Red","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Blue","pendex":{}}]},{"id":3,"random":283521499,"question":"","category":"Generic","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Green","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Yellow","pendex":{}}]},{"id":4,"random":816490048,"question":"","category":"Generic","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Orange","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Blue","pendex":{}}]},{"id":5,"random":354714158,"question":"","category":"Generic","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Blue","pendex":{}},{"answer":"White","pendex":{}}]},{"id":6,"random":993721708,"question":"","category":"Generic","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"White","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Black","pendex":{"Ninja":1}}]},{"id":7,"random":957235250,"question":"","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Half Full","pendex":{"Optimistic":1}},{"answer":"Half Empty","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":8,"random":114266098,"question":"","category":"Life Skills","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Couch","pendex":{"Lazy":1}},{"answer":"Hike","pendex":{"Active":1}}]},{"id":9,"random":412526908,"question":"","category":"Humorous","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"SJP","pendex":{"Social":1}},{"answer":"Horse","pendex":{"Beastmastery":1,"Reddit":1}}]},{"id":10,"random":292325449,"question":"","category":"Humorous","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Badluck Brian","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1}},{"answer":"Scumbag Steve","pendex":{"Narcissistic":1}}]},{"id":11,"random":961023879,"question":"","category":"Humorous","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Show Case #1","pendex":{"Badluck":1}},{"answer":"Show Case #2","pendex":{"Goodluck":1}}]},{"id":12,"random":58967698,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Twilight","pendex":{"Romantic":1}},{"answer":"Harry Potter","pendex":{"Escapist":1}}]},{"id":13,"random":649539616,"question":"","category":"Life Skills","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Eat at home","pendex":{"Cooking":1}},{"answer":"Dine Out","pendex":{"Lazy":1}}]},{"id":14,"random":853692033,"question":"","category":"Internet Savvy","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Yahoo News","pendex":{"Internet Challenged":1}},{"answer":"Other","pendex":{"Internet Savvy":1}}]},{"id":15,"random":132621779,"question":"","category":"Internet Savvy","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Reddit","pendex":{"Internet Savvy":1}},{"answer":"Read what","pendex":{"Internet Challenged":1}}]},{"id":16,"random":462751954,"question":"","category":"Internet Savvy","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Chrome","pendex":{"Internet Savvy":1}},{"answer":"Internet Explorer","pendex":{"Internet Challenged":1}}]},{"id":17,"random":551740213,"question":"","category":"Internet Savvy","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Chive is a forum","pendex":{"Internet Savvy":1}},{"answer":"Chive is a food","pendex":{"Cooking":1}}]},{"id":18,"random":600251660,"question":"","category":"Tech","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Buy a computer","pendex":{"Social":1}},{"answer":"Build a computer","pendex":{"Antisocial":1}}]},{"id":19,"random":373872050,"question":"","category":"Life Skills","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Groups","pendex":{"Gregarious":1}},{"answer":"Alone","pendex":{"Hermit":1}}]},{"id":20,"random":501084994,"question":"","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Hey","pendex":{"Informal":1}},{"answer":"Hello","pendex":{"Informal":1}}]},{"id":21,"random":759269267,"question":"","category":"Humorous","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Gandalf","pendex":{"Escapist":1}},{"answer":"Neo","pendex":{"Narcissistic":1}}]},{"id":22,"random":503691998,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"You Guys","pendex":{"Sophisticated":1}},{"answer":"Y'all","pendex":{"Uncultured":1}}]},{"id":23,"random":262130095,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Soda","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Pop","pendex":{}}]},{"id":24,"random":40874058,"question":"","category":"Video Gaming","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"EQ","pendex":{"OldSchool":1}},{"answer":"WoW","pendex":{"Modern":1}}]},{"id":25,"random":975868338,"question":"","category":"Video Gaming","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Console","pendex":{"Independent":1}},{"answer":"PC","pendex":{}}]},{"id":26,"random":202166572,"question":"","category":"Video Gaming","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Tank","pendex":{"Leadership":1}},{"answer":"Healer","pendex":{"Focus":1}}]},{"id":27,"random":348126742,"question":"","category":"Video Gaming","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Healer","pendex":{"Focus":1}},{"answer":"DPS","pendex":{}}]},{"id":28,"random":383277188,"question":"","category":"Video Gaming","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Tank","pendex":{"Leadership":1}},{"answer":"DPS","pendex":{}}]},{"id":29,"random":994185366,"question":"","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Loud ","pendex":{"Social":1}},{"answer":"Quiet","pendex":{"Antisocial":1}}]},{"id":30,"random":376739575,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Book","pendex":{"Sophisticated":1}},{"answer":"Movie","pendex":{"Outgoing":1}}]},{"id":31,"random":818666272,"question":"","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Dream","pendex":{"Escapist":1}},{"answer":"Real","pendex":{"Realist":1}}]},{"id":32,"random":291216144,"question":"","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Finger painting","pendex":{"Informal":1}},{"answer":"Paint brush painting","pendex":{"Formal":1}}]},{"id":33,"random":455253835,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"DIY","pendex":{"Crafting":1}},{"answer":"Professional","pendex":{"Lazy":1}}]},{"id":34,"random":700940106,"question":"You see your car as","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Transportation","pendex":{"Realist":1}},{"answer":"A way to express yourself","pendex":{"Escapist":1}}]},{"id":35,"random":496479545,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Pickup truck","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Compact Car","pendex":{}}]},{"id":36,"random":535876077,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Sports Car","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Compact Car","pendex":{}}]},{"id":37,"random":707532711,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Compact Car","pendex":{}},{"answer":"SUV","pendex":{}}]},{"id":38,"random":119682350,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"SUV","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Sports Car","pendex":{}}]},{"id":39,"random":599748674,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Pickup truck","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Sports Car","pendex":{}}]},{"id":40,"random":966983066,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"SUV","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Pickup Truck","pendex":{}}]},{"id":41,"random":534214474,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Luxury Sedan","pendex":{}},{"answer":"SUV","pendex":{}}]},{"id":42,"random":62440250,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Pickup Truck","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Luxury Sedan","pendex":{}}]},{"id":43,"random":290263799,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Compact Car","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Luxury Sedan","pendex":{}}]},{"id":44,"random":288408847,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Luxury Sedan","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Sports Car","pendex":{}}]},{"id":45,"random":577078531,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Fall","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Summer","pendex":{}}]},{"id":46,"random":950448658,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Winter","pendex":{"Antisocial":1}},{"answer":"Summer","pendex":{}}]},{"id":47,"random":801868891,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Summer","pendex":{"Social":1}},{"answer":"Spring","pendex":{}}]},{"id":48,"random":303659287,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Spring","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Winter","pendex":{}}]},{"id":49,"random":988373,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Fall","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Spring","pendex":{}}]},{"id":50,"random":18835278,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Fall","pendex":{}},{"answer":"Winter","pendex":{}}]},{"id":51,"random":859798223,"question":"","category":"Technology","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Android","pendex":{"Independent":1}},{"answer":"Apple","pendex":{"Expensive":1}}]},{"id":52,"random":385061563,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Toilet paper over","pendex":{"Sophisticated":1}},{"answer":"Toilet paper under","pendex":{"Uncultured":1}}]},{"id":53,"random":315200270,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Drink from glass","pendex":{"Sophisticated":1}},{"answer":"Drink from jug","pendex":{"Lazy":1}}]},{"id":54,"random":41971113,"question":"You put your dirty clothes","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"On the floor","pendex":{"Lazy":1}},{"answer":"In a basket","pendex":{"Sophisticated":1}}]},{"id":55,"random":176700655,"question":"Your sink is usually","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Empty","pendex":{"Clean":1}},{"answer":"Filled with dishes","pendex":{"Dirty":1}}]},{"id":56,"random":315972537,"question":"Cake","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Blow out candles","pendex":{"Confident":1,"Escapist":1}},{"answer":"Happy Birthday to the Ground","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":57,"random":295972329,"question":"","category":"","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Autumn","pendex":{"Classy":1}},{"answer":"Fall","pendex":{}}]},{"id":58,"random":23958965,"question":"You wear your sandals","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Socks on","pendex":{"Uncultured":1}},{"answer":"Socks off","pendex":{"Sophisticated":1}}]},{"id":59,"random":42594150,"question":"","category":"Technology","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"AMD","pendex":{"Independent":1}},{"answer":"Intel","pendex":{"Expensive":1}}]},{"id":60,"random":457088385,"question":"","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Expect the best","pendex":{"Optimistic":1}},{"answer":"Expect the worst","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":61,"random":639532490,"question":"Do you find it easy to relax?","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Yes","pendex":{"Optimistic":1}},{"answer":"No","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":62,"random":296063766,"question":"Something will go wrong","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Nope! I got this :)","pendex":{"Optimistic":1}},{"answer":"Yeah...that's me.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":63,"random":413688293,"question":"Friends are","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Bothersome","pendex":{"Independent":1,"Antisocial":1}},{"answer":"Required","pendex":{"Social":1,"Dependent":1}}]},{"id":64,"random":395944015,"question":"","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Life sucks","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1}},{"answer":"Life is awesome","pendex":{"Optimistic":1}}]},{"id":65,"random":315284920,"question":"How do you feel about the lottery?","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"I'M GONNA WIN","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Escapist":1}},{"answer":"The odds are forever not in my favor","pendex":{"Realist":1,"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":66,"random":749019885,"question":"Good things usually happen to me.","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"For the most part!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Escapist":1,"Goodluck":1}},{"answer":"Not really. My luck sucks.","pendex":{"Realist":1,"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1}}]},{"id":67,"random":448957834,"question":"You're having a hard time. Things are","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Going to get better.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1}},{"answer":"Only going to get worse.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":68,"random":852947890,"question":{},"category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"There's always a chance!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1}},{"answer":"I'm f***ed.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Realist":1}}]},{"id":69,"random":586203965,"question":"The girl/guy of your dreams shows up at a party you were on the fence about going to.","category":"Psychological","linked":"X","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"I knew this was a good idea.","pendex":{"Confident":1,"Optimistic":1}},{"answer":"I'm so lucky!","pendex":{"Goodluck":1,"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":70,"random":120534156,"question":"She/He doesn't even notice you.","category":"Psychological","linked":"X","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Because I didn't introduce myself.","pendex":{"Confident":1,"Optimistic":1,"Gregarious":1,"Outgoing":1}},{"answer":"Why would she?","pendex":{"Antisocial":1,"Pessimistic":1,"Hermit":1}}]},{"id":71,"random":143545683,"question":"The party you planned literally gets rained on.","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Confident":1,"Optimistic":1}},{"answer":"My luck sucks.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1}}]},{"id":72,"random":637806123,"question":"You've just lost 5lbs towards your targeted weight.","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"My hard work is paying off!","pendex":{"Confident":1,"Optimistic":1,"Strength":1}},{"answer":"I hope I keep losing weight...","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":73,"random":316685661,"question":"You see a penny while walking downtown.","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"You pickup the penny.","pendex":{"Dirty":1,"Optimistic":1}},{"answer":"You ignore the penny.","pendex":{"Realist":1,"Pessimistic":1,"Clean":1}}]},{"id":74,"random":356936430,"question":"The penny turns into flaming two handed sword.","category":"Life Choices","linked":"X - PLOT TWIST","achievement":"Lord of Pennies - \"One penny flaming two handed sword to rule them all\"","answers":[{"answer":"Damn I'm good!","pendex":{"Confident":1,"Strength":1,"Escapist":1}},{"answer":"You drop it because you think it will burn you.","pendex":{"Realist":1,"Pessimistic":1,"Badluck":1}}]},{"id":75,"random":564518979,"question":"You get honked at in traffic.","category":"Psychological","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"They must be having a bad day.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Sophisticated":1}},{"answer":"YOU SON OF A B****. I'LL KILL YOU! AND YOUR FAMILY!","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Uncultured":1}}]},{"id":76,"random":876947617,"question":"","category":"Life Choices","linked":"","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"Kitten","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Classy":1,"Internet Savvy":1}},{"answer":"Razorblade","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Antisocial":1}}]},{"id":77,"random":497696620,"question":{},"category":"Life Choices","linked":"X","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"I always look good.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Classy":1,"Confident":1,"Social":1,"Outgoing":1}},{"answer":"They are just being nice...","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Antisocial":1,"Hermit":1}}]},{"id":78,"random":72811317,"question":"The outfit is a banana costume.","category":"Life Choices","linked":"X - PLOT TWIST","achievement":"Wardrobe \"Slip\"-up - \"I dare say the banana owes me one for making it look good\"","answers":[{"answer":"I make a good banana.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Classy":1,"Confident":1,"Social":1}},{"answer":"Oh god...is this a nightmare? WAKE ME UP!","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1,"Antisocial":1,"Hermit":1}}]},{"id":79,"random":207197234,"question":"You're sore the next day from an intense new workout.","category":"Psychological","linked":"X","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"I must have worked hard!","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1}},{"answer":"I'm so out of shape.","pendex":{"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":80,"random":565569204,"question":{},"category":"Psychological","linked":"X - PLOT TWIST","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1,"Dangerous":1,"Focus":1}},{"answer":"What the hell was I thinking? That's insanity...","pendex":{"Safety":1,"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":81,"random":884881171,"question":{},"category":"Psychological","linked":"X - PLOT TWIST","achievement":"","answers":[{"answer":"It could still be worse.","pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Confident":1,"Dangerous":1}},{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Safety":1,"Pessimistic":1}}]},{"id":82,"random":43578458,"question":{},"category":"Psychological","linked":"X - PLOT TWIST","achievement":{},"answers":[{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Optimistic":1,"Dangerous":1,"Confident":1}},{"answer":{},"pendex":{"Safety":1,"Pessimistic":1}}]}]
